[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1971 David Bowies song Life on Mars? appeared on which of his albums?", "correct_answer": "Hunky Dory", "incorrect_answers": ["Young Americans", "Space Oddity", "Earthling"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The carbonated beverage Fanta is a product of which company?", "correct_answer": "Coca-Cola Bottling Co.", "incorrect_answers": ["Royal Crown (RC)", "Independently owned and operated", "Pepsi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The mercenary group, featured in the movie Blood Diamond, was loosely based on Executive Outcomes, a real mercenary group that once operated in Africa. In which country was Executive Outcomes based?", "correct_answer": "South Africa", "incorrect_answers": ["Libya", "Sudan", "Somalia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What crime is Randall Bragg, played by Jeremy Irons in Appaloosa, accused of?", "correct_answer": "Murder", "incorrect_answers": ["Armed Bank Robbery", "Stealing horses", "Rape"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which European Union member was the first country to reject communist rule and thus sparkle the liberation of so called Eastern Block?", "correct_answer": "Poland", "incorrect_answers": ["Czech Republic", "Romania", "Germany"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year was 7 Up first marketed as 100% Natural?", "correct_answer": "2006", "incorrect_answers": ["2003", "2005", "2004"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the weight of the smallest known bird egg on the planet?", "correct_answer": "0,5 grams", "incorrect_answers": ["2,5 grams", "5 grams", "1 gram"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The worlds strongest lager is named after Santa Claus.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Hall-H\u00e9roult chemical process is used for the production of what?", "correct_answer": "Aluminum", "incorrect_answers": ["Zirconium", "Titanium", "Methane"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This cocktail is made of 2 oz vodka, 3 oz cranberry juice, 2 oz grapefruit juice. The ingredients are shaken with ice and then strain into a highball glass.", "correct_answer": "Sea Breeze", "incorrect_answers": ["Bloody Mary", "Caipirinha", "Kamikaze"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to The Bible, how long did Jonah stay in the whale (i.e. in the leviathan)?", "correct_answer": "3 days and 3 nights", "incorrect_answers": ["40 days and 40 nights", "0 days and 0 nights", "120 years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The constant anticyclonic storm on Jupiter which can be seen through telescopes from Earth is called by what name?", "correct_answer": "The Great Red Spot", "incorrect_answers": ["The Green Belt", "The Red Eye", "The Bright White Eye"]}]